<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-02T16:51:49-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Elizabeth Cheapoo]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week9]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/13/week9/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-13T17:41:24-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/13/week9</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week has been very busy
Too many work to do with so little time.
I don&rsquo;t know how to combine code school homework
and tons of other assignments on my worksheet with learning new things
I&rsquo;m honestly burning out and wating for the program to end.
I have a lot of things to learn even with the help of others,
I&rsquo;m not sure if I&rsquo;m ready to start doing stuff with what I have learnt so far
I will keep learning to get better even after I&rsquo;m done with the program.
I just want to get better every week.
I hope next week will be better.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-09-week8-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/09/week8-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-09T11:40:42-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/09/week8-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 8 is better than last week.
I was able to get help through extra class on the weekend.
I&rsquo;m really happy to learn how to answer some difficult questions.
The class helped me to understand a big part of my work that I find really hard.
I&rsquo;m learning to solve part of my work but I still have a long way to go.
I hope next week will be better or at least, as good as this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-30-week7-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/30/week7-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-30T11:39:03-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/30/week7-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I&rsquo;m still confused. I&rsquo;m trying not to give up.
I&rsquo;m working really hard to get it but I keep getting stuck all over again.
I still have a lot of work to finish up. I&rsquo;m frustrated, confused and stressed. Any help would do at this point.
I&rsquo;m still hanging in there because I really want to know this stuff.
A little direction will help a lot. I have tried different coding apps and code school on my own.
They help a little but when I try to apply what I learned to my homework, I find it difficult. I&rsquo;m worried but hopeful that week 8 will be better.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015.07.23-week-6-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/23/week-6-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-23T11:36:31-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/23/week-6-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>week six i&rsquo;m still having a hard time but i&rsquo;m getting as much help as i can. There is so much work to do and
i&rsquo;ve been really depressed for weeks but i&rsquo;m
trying to count my blessings instead of complaining about what is going wrong in my life.
I&rsquo;m dealing with some personal issues which is getting in the way of stuffs that I&rsquo;m learning.
It is difficult for me to understand alot of the concepts
and it is adding to my frustration.
Even with the help i&rsquo;ve got, I still have a lot of work to do.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-16-week-5-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/16/week-5-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-16T11:35:37-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/16/week-5-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 5 is not so bad I&rsquo;m lost but not with everything.
Things are starting to make sense little by little.
Beginning to learn things on my own as much as I can
but I could use more help.
If I have a partner who can help with explaining things to me, I  will be able to know more.
I will use what I learn to my work.
Learning on my own is good but sometimes I get lost and I cannot get others to explain things to me.
I am doing all I can to be better but more help would go a long way me.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-09-week-4-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/09/week-4-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-09T11:34:17-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/09/week-4-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I feel more lost then ever.
I&rsquo;m starting to think that I&rsquo;m going to fail this class.
I don&rsquo;t know what to do anymore.
No matter what I do, I don&rsquo;t feel like I can keep up with everyone in the class.
It is frustrating to see that even with all my effort, I am still behind on my worksheet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02-week-3-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/02/week-3-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-02T11:32:05-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/02/week-3-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week three was very hard for me chapter 2 was not easy
i just wish to have someone that we can work together with than to be doing it
all by myself. I feel that we are going too fast with chapter 2 and it is becoming difficult to catch up. The chapter has a lot of ideas that are not clear.
I don&rsquo;t have a foundation in coding so i need more help with the chapter. I hope week 4 will be better.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015.06.26-week2-blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/week2-blogpost/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T11:30:44-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/week2-blogpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 2 to me was hard, but I think I&rsquo;m starting to learn something. I&rsquo;m just happy that I&rsquo;m not as lost as i was the first day I started. The JS online book helped a lot. So far I&rsquo;m happy with this YWEBCA.I will try read more of the online book to get my stuff done. Things are hard because I am just learning the language of coding. The book is helping me a little bit but I still need extra help. I&rsquo;m happy to be a part of the program and I hope next week will be better. Week 3 here come!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-19-Welcome Lizziec11]]></title>
    <link href="http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/Welcome-lizziec11/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T16:46:43-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://lizziec11.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/Welcome-lizziec11</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just like the other week, I have learned a lot but there is so much to learn. The time is short, a lot of work to do.
I don&rsquo;t think I understand everything I need to know at this point, all I&rsquo;m trying to do at this moment is keep learning.
I hope to improve on the little I&rsquo;ve figured out.
I&rsquo;ll still get assistance from anybody in the program who is willing to help out.
My goal is to make sure I become really fluent in the course.
Learning new things is very difficult and I want to be sure that I&rsquo;m  doing the right thing.
I&rsquo;m drained already, I can&rsquo;t keep up with a lot of my classmates and the work we have to do.
I&rsquo;ll make sure I keep working until I can be comfortable to do something with what I&rsquo;ve learn so far.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
